bacb.com.au 2017-06-06

# Privacy

This privacy policy explains what information we collect about you, how we may use it, and the steps we take to ensure that it is kept secure. We also explain your rights and how to contact us.

Please note, this website contains links to other websites which are provided for your convenience. We are only responsible for the privacy practices and security of this site. We recommend that you check the privacy and security policies and procedures of each and every other website that you visit.

### Consent

By using this website and giving your information to us, you indicate your consent to us and our third party suppliers and our related companies collecting, using and disclosing your personal information in accordance with the terms set out in this policy.

### What information do we collect?

In order to provide you with services, we may collect personal information about you from our website, telephone conversations, e-mails and written and verbal communications. We may, for example, keep a record of your name, address, delivery address, e-mail address, telephone number and banking details. We may also record details of any disability or health needs you may have. Sensitive information will only be used and disclosed for the purpose for which it was disclosed to us or for a directly related secondary purpose.

We may supplement the information that you provide with other information that we obtain from our dealings with you or which we receive from other organisations, for example, our suppliers.

### How will we use your information?

All personal information that we obtain about you will be recorded, used and protected by us in accordance with the Privacy Act 1988 and this privacy policy. We will primarily use your personal information to provide our products and services to you and, for example:

  *   to represent you in legal and business transactions and matters;
  *   to communicate with you;
  *   for record keeping purposes;
  *   to improve the quality of our service;
  *   to update you on relevant legal developments;
  *   for market research;
  *   to track activity on our website; and
  *   to co-operate with law enforcement agencies as (required by law).

### Disclosure of your information

In order to provide our services to you, we may need to appoint other organisations to carry out some of the processing activities on our behalf. These will include, for example, barristers, investigators, foreign law firms to obtain advise on foreign matters, delivery organisations, third party suppliers and agents. These third parties may have access to information needed to perform their function but cannot use that information for other purposes.

### Use of your information outside Australia

We do not normally send information overseas, but, if the circumstances require we may need to do so in order to provide our services to you.

Some of the organisations (for example, software suppliers, cloud suppliers or agents, etc.) to which we may disclose your personal information are situated outside of Australia. In order to meet your requirements, we may need to transfer your personal information to these countries. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that any organisation to whom we release your information will comply with the Australian Privacy Act 1988.

### Analytics

We may use products such as Google Analytics and HubSpot to analyse the audience statistics of our website to improve our content. No personal information is collect from Google Analytics.

We may use products to analysis audience statistic of our website to improve our content.

### Cookies

In common with many other website operators, we may use standard technology called 'cookies' on site. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive and they are used to record how you navigate this website on each visit.

Cookies that are used in any part of our website will not be utilised for collecting personally identifiable information and will only be used for internal management purposes.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent cookies being stored. Please note, if you do turn cookies off this will limit the service that we are able to provide to you.

For further information on cookies and how to switch them off see www.allaboutcookies.org.

### Information about other people

If you provide information to us about a third party (such as your directors, employees or someone you have business dealing with) you must ensure that you are entitled to disclose that information to us and that you have fully complied with the Privacy Act 1988 in relation to the collection, use or disclosure of that information.

### Security of information

We take the security of your personal information seriously.

All reasonable steps are taken to ensure that all information is treated confidentially, kept secure and protected against unauthorised use and is maintained only for the purpose for which it is intended.

### Direct Marketing

We may use your personal information to notify you of services that we may be able to offer you from time to time. We do not sell, licence or, in any other way, distribute your personal information to any other company for the purpose of direct marketing and will do so without your express written consent. You may opt out of receiving any publications, newsletter or other marketing product at anytime.

### Changes to this privacy policy

We aim to meet high standards and our policies and procedures are, therefore, constantly under review. From time to time we may change our security and privacy policies. Accordingly we recommend that you check this page periodically in order to review our current policies.

### Updating and correcting information

All reasonable steps are taken to correct information held where the information is not accurate, up-to-date and complete.

You may correct your personal information by e-mailing us at [support@bigair.net.au](mailto:support@bigair.net.au) or by changing your profile on our website. Please include your name, address and/or e-mail address when you contact us as this helps us to ensure that we accept amendments only from the correct person. We encourage you to promptly update your personal information if it changes.

### Your rights to access your personal information

You have the right to access your personal information and requests for information about our privacy policy are welcomed. You will need to provide proof of identify before access will be granted, and access may be denied if one of the exceptions set out in the Privacy Act applies.

### How to contact us

If you would like any further information or have any comments about our privacy policy or any other aspect of our website or service, please contact us at:

BigAir Group Pty Ltd  
Level 1, 203 Pacific Highway  
St Leonards, NSW 2065, AUSTRALIA 

Or you may contact the office at the Australian Information Commission at [www.oaic.gov.au](http://www.oaic.gov.au/).
